export const quiz = {
    totalQuestions: 20,
    questions: [
      {
        id: 1,
        question: 'What is the result of `typeof typeof 1`?',
        answers: ['number', 'string', 'object', 'undefined'],
        correctAnswer: 'string',
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question: 'What will `console.log(1 === true)` output?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: 'false',
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: 'What is the result of `"hello" instanceof Object`?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: 'false',
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: 'What does `console.log([10] === [10])` return?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: 'false',
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        question: 'What will the following code output: `console.log(1 + "2" + "2")`?',
        answers: ['122', '5', '14', 'undefined'],
        correctAnswer: '122',
      },
      {
        id: 6,
        question: 'What is the output of `console.log(3 + 2 + "7")`?',
        answers: ['12', '327', '57', 'undefined'],
        correctAnswer: '57',
      },
      {
        id: 7,
        question: 'What will be the output of `console.log(Math.max())`?',
        answers: ['0', 'undefined', 'Infinity', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: '-Infinity',
      },
      {
        id: 8,
        question: 'What will be the output of `console.log(1 < 2 < 3)`?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: 'true',
      },
      {
        id: 9,
        question: 'What is the result of `"5" - 3`?',
        answers: ['2', '8', 'NaN', 'undefined'],
        correctAnswer: '2',
      },
      {
        id: 10,
        question: 'What will `console.log(1 - "1")` output?',
        answers: ['0', '1', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: '0',
      },
      {
        id: 11,
        question: 'What is the output of `console.log(typeof NaN)`?',
        answers: ['number', 'string', 'NaN', 'undefined'],
        correctAnswer: 'number',
      },
      {
        id: 12,
        question: 'What does the following code return: `console.log(typeof (typeof 1))`?',
        answers: ['number', 'string', 'object', 'undefined'],
        correctAnswer: 'string',
      },
      {
        id: 13,
        question: 'What will the following code output: `console.log([] + {})`?',
        answers: ['[object Object]', '{}', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: '[object Object]',
      },
      {
        id: 14,
        question: 'What will the output of `console.log(1 + 2 + "3")` be?',
        answers: ['33', '123', '6', 'undefined'],
        correctAnswer: '33',
      },
      {
        id: 15,
        question: 'What will be the output of `console.log(+"hello")`?',
        answers: ['NaN', 'SyntaxError', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: 'NaN',
      },
      {
        id: 16,
        question: 'What will the following code output: `console.log(!!"false")`?',
        answers: ['false', 'true', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: 'true',
      },
      {
        id: 17,
        question: 'What is the result of `console.log([] + [])`?',
        answers: ['[]', '{}', '0', 'undefined'],
        correctAnswer: '',
      },
      {
        id: 18,
        question: 'What will be the output of `console.log(0.1 + 0.2 === 0.3)`?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: 'false',
      },
      {
        id: 19,
        question: 'What will be the output of the following code: `console.log(typeof typeof 1)`?',
        answers: ['number', 'string', 'object', 'undefined'],
        correctAnswer: 'string',
      },
      {
        id: 20,
        question: 'What is the output of `console.log(1 === true)`?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: 'false',
      },
      {
        id: 21,
        question: 'What will be the result of `console.log(typeof null)`?',
        answers: ['object', 'null', 'undefined', 'string'],
        correctAnswer: 'object',
      },
      {
        id: 22,
        question: 'What does `console.log([] == ![])` output?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'NaN'],
        correctAnswer: 'true',
      },
      {
        id: 23,
        question: 'What will the following code output: `console.log(2 ** 3)`?',
        answers: ['8', '6', '9', 'SyntaxError'],
        correctAnswer: '8',
      },
      {
        id: 24,
        question: 'What does `console.log(0 == false)` return?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'TypeError', 'undefined'],
        correctAnswer: 'true',
      },
      {
        id: 25,
        question: 'What will `console.log([] == "")` output?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'NaN'],
        correctAnswer: 'true',
      },
      {
        id: 26,
        question: 'What will be the output of `console.log(typeof undefined)`?',
        answers: ['undefined', 'string', 'object', 'null'],
        correctAnswer: 'undefined',
      },
      {
        id: 27,
        question: 'What is the result of `console.log(1 + true)`?',
        answers: ['2', '1', 'true', 'undefined'],
        correctAnswer: '2',
      },
      {
        id: 28,
        question: 'What will `console.log(parseInt("10.5"))` return?',
        answers: ['10', '10.5', 'NaN', 'SyntaxError'],
        correctAnswer: '10',
      },
      {
        id: 29,
        question: 'What will `console.log(!!0)` output?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: 'false',
      },
      {
        id: 30,
        question: 'What is the result of `console.log([1, 2, 3] instanceof Array)`?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: 'true',
      },
      {
        id: 31,
        question: 'What will the following code return: `console.log(Number("10px"))`?',
        answers: ['10', 'NaN', 'SyntaxError', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: 'NaN',
      },
      {
        id: 32,
        question: 'What does `console.log(!!"0")` output?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: 'true',
      },
      {
        id: 33,
        question: 'What will be the output of `console.log([] == ![])`?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'NaN'],
        correctAnswer: 'true',
      },
      {
        id: 34,
        question: 'What does the following code return: `console.log(null == undefined)`?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'NaN', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: 'true',
      },
      {
        id: 35,
        question: 'What will the following code output: `console.log(+"")`?',
        answers: ['NaN', '0', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: '0',
      },
      {
        id: 36,
        question: 'What is the result of `console.log([] + {})`?',
        answers: ['[object Object]', '{}', 'null', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: '[object Object]',
      },
      {
        id: 37,
        question: 'What will be the output of `console.log({} + {})`?',
        answers: ['[object Object][object Object]', 'NaN', 'TypeError', '[object Object]'],
        correctAnswer: '[object Object][object Object]',
      },
      {
        id: 38,
        question: 'What will the following code return: `console.log(3 / 0)`?',
        answers: ['Infinity', 'NaN', 'undefined', '0'],
        correctAnswer: 'Infinity',
      },
      {
        id: 39,
        question: 'What will be the output of `console.log("2" * "3")`?',
        answers: ['6', 'NaN', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: '6',
      },
      {
        id: 40,
        question: 'What is the result of `console.log(+"2.5")`?',
        answers: ['2.5', 'NaN', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: '2.5',
      },
      {
        id: 41,
        question: 'What does `console.log(typeof NaN)` output?',
        answers: ['number', 'NaN', 'undefined', 'object'],
        correctAnswer: 'number',
      },
      {
        id: 42,
        question: 'What will the following code output: `console.log([] + {})`?',
        answers: ['[object Object]', '{}', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: '[object Object]',
      },
      {
        id: 43,
        question: 'What will `console.log(null === undefined)` output?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: 'false',
      },
      {
        id: 44,
        question: 'What will `console.log(1 < 2 < 3)` return?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: 'true',
      },
      {
        id: 45,
        question: 'What does `console.log("foo" + +"bar")` return?',
        answers: ['fooNaN', 'foobar', 'SyntaxError', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: 'fooNaN',
      },
      {
        id: 46,
        question: 'What is the result of `typeof function() {}`?',
        answers: ['function', 'object', 'undefined', 'string'],
        correctAnswer: 'function',
      },
      {
        id: 47,
        question: 'What will `console.log(0 == "0")` return?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'TypeError', 'undefined'],
        correctAnswer: 'true',
      },
      {
        id: 48,
        question: 'What is the result of `console.log(0 === "0")`?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: 'false',
      },
      {
        id: 49,
        question: 'What does `console.log({}.toString())` output?',
        answers: ['[object Object]', 'undefined', '{}', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: '[object Object]',
      },
      {
        id: 50,
        question: 'What will `console.log(Object.is(NaN, NaN))` return?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: 'true',
      },
      {
        id: 51,
        question: 'What does `console.log(typeof [])` output?',
        answers: ['object', 'array', 'undefined', 'null'],
        correctAnswer: 'object',
      },
      {
        id: 52,
        question: 'What will `console.log([] === [])` return?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: 'false',
      },
      {
        id: 53,
        question: 'What does `console.log(1 - "1")` output?',
        answers: ['0', 'NaN', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: '0',
      },
      {
        id: 54,
        question: 'What is the result of `console.log(true + false)`?',
        answers: ['1', 'true', 'false', 'NaN'],
        correctAnswer: '1',
      },
      {
        id: 55,
        question: 'What will `console.log(+"10px")` return?',
        answers: ['NaN', '10', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: 'NaN',
      },
      {
        id: 56,
        question: 'What does `console.log([] instanceof Object)` return?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'NaN'],
        correctAnswer: 'true',
      },
      {
        id: 57,
        question: 'What will be the output of `console.log(2 + "2" - "1")`?',
        answers: ['21', '3', 'NaN', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: '21',
      },
      {
        id: 58,
        question: 'What will the following code output: `console.log(!"hello")`?',
        answers: ['false', 'true', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: 'false',
      },
      {
        id: 59,
        question: 'What is the result of `console.log(Math.max())`?',
        answers: ['-Infinity', 'Infinity', '0', 'NaN'],
        correctAnswer: '-Infinity',
      },
      {
        id: 60,
        question: 'What will `console.log(undefined + 1)` return?',
        answers: ['NaN', '1', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: 'NaN',
      },
      {
        id: 61,
        question: 'What will `console.log(1 / 0)` output?',
        answers: ['Infinity', 'NaN', 'undefined', '0'],
        correctAnswer: 'Infinity',
      },
      {
        id: 62,
        question: 'What is the result of `typeof NaN === "number"`?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'NaN', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: 'true',
      },
      {
        id: 63,
        question: 'What will `console.log("10" - "5")` return?',
        answers: ['5', 'NaN', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: '5',
      },
      {
        id: 64,
        question: 'What does `console.log(0 || 1)` return?',
        answers: ['0', '1', 'false', 'undefined'],
        correctAnswer: '1',
      },
      {
        id: 65,
        question: 'What will `console.log(0 && 1)` return?',
        answers: ['0', '1', 'false', 'undefined'],
        correctAnswer: '0',
      },
      {
        id: 66,
        question: 'What is the result of `typeof []`?',
        answers: ['object', 'array', 'undefined', 'null'],
        correctAnswer: 'object',
      },
      {
        id: 67,
        question: 'What will `console.log([1, 2, 3] + [4, 5, 6])` return?',
        answers: ['1,2,34,5,6', 'NaN', 'SyntaxError', 'undefined'],
        correctAnswer: '1,2,34,5,6',
      },
      {
        id: 68,
        question: 'What does `console.log("5" + 3)` return?',
        answers: ['53', '8', 'NaN', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: '53',
      },
      {
        id: 69,
        question: 'What will `console.log(typeof (1 + "2"))` return?',
        answers: ['string', 'number', 'undefined', 'object'],
        correctAnswer: 'string',
      },
      {
        id: 70,
        question: 'What does `console.log(typeof Infinity)` output?',
        answers: ['number', 'undefined', 'object', 'string'],
        correctAnswer: 'number',
      },
      {
        id: 71,
        question: 'What is the result of `console.log(parseInt("123abc"))`?',
        answers: ['123', 'NaN', '0', 'SyntaxError'],
        correctAnswer: '123',
      },
      {
        id: 72,
        question: 'What will `console.log(null + 1)` return?',
        answers: ['1', 'NaN', 'null', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: '1',
      },
      {
        id: 73,
        question: 'What does `console.log([] + [])` output?',
        answers: ['""', '[]', 'null', 'undefined'],
        correctAnswer: '""',
      },
      {
        id: 74,
        question: 'What is the result of `console.log(typeof true)`?',
        answers: ['boolean', 'object', 'string', 'undefined'],
        correctAnswer: 'boolean',
      },
      {
        id: 75,
        question: 'What will `console.log(1 < 2 < 1)` return?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: 'true',
      },
      {
        id: 76,
        question: 'What is the result of `console.log(1 == "1")`?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'NaN'],
        correctAnswer: 'true',
      },
      {
        id: 77,
        question: 'What does `console.log(null === null)` return?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: 'true',
      },
      {
        id: 78,
        question: 'What is the result of `console.log([1,2,3].length)`?',
        answers: ['3', 'undefined', '2', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: '3',
      },
      {
        id: 79,
        question: 'What does `console.log(new Date() instanceof Date)` return?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: 'true',
      },
      {
        id: 80,
        question: 'What will `console.log(typeof 123n)` output?',
        answers: ['bigint', 'number', 'NaN', 'undefined'],
        correctAnswer: 'bigint',
      },
      {
        id: 81,
        question: 'What is the result of `console.log(5 % 2)`?',
        answers: ['1', '0', '5', 'undefined'],
        correctAnswer: '1',
      },
      {
        id: 82,
        question: 'What will `console.log(!!1)` return?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'NaN'],
        correctAnswer: 'true',
      },
      {
        id: 83,
        question: 'What does `console.log(typeof undefined)` output?',
        answers: ['undefined', 'string', 'object', 'null'],
        correctAnswer: 'undefined',
      },
      {
        id: 84,
        question: 'What will `console.log(+"123")` return?',
        answers: ['123', 'NaN', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: '123',
      },
      {
        id: 85,
        question: 'What is the result of `console.log(5 < 3)`?',
        answers: ['false', 'true', 'undefined', 'NaN'],
        correctAnswer: 'false',
      },
      {
        id: 86,
        question: 'What will `console.log(typeof {})` output?',
        answers: ['object', 'undefined', 'null', 'NaN'],
        correctAnswer: 'object',
      },
      {
        id: 87,
        question: 'What does `console.log([] == "")` output?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'NaN'],
        correctAnswer: 'true',
      },
      {
        id: 88,
        question: 'What is the result of `console.log("2" - "1")`?',
        answers: ['1', 'NaN', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: '1',
      },
      {
        id: 89,
        question: 'What will `console.log(1 == true)` return?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'NaN'],
        correctAnswer: 'true',
      },
      {
        id: 90,
        question: 'What does `console.log(0 === false)` return?',
        answers: ['false', 'true', 'undefined', 'NaN'],
        correctAnswer: 'false',
      },
      {
        id: 91,
        question: 'What is the result of `typeof null === "object"`?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'NaN', 'undefined'],
        correctAnswer: 'true',
      },
      {
        id: 92,
        question: 'What will `console.log(2 + "2" - 1)` return?',
        answers: ['21', 'NaN', '3', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: '21',
      },
      {
        id: 93,
        question: 'What does `console.log(typeof NaN)` return?',
        answers: ['number', 'NaN', 'undefined', 'object'],
        correctAnswer: 'number',
      },
      {
        id: 94,
        question: 'What will `console.log([] === ![])` output?',
        answers: ['false', 'true', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: 'false',
      },
      {
        id: 95,
        question: 'What is the result of `console.log([1, 2] + [3, 4])`?',
        answers: ['1,23,4', 'NaN', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: '1,23,4',
      },
      {
        id: 96,
        question: 'What will `console.log([] == false)` output?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: 'true',
      },
      {
        id: 97,
        question: 'What is the result of `typeof {} + "[]"`?',
        answers: ['[object Object][]', 'undefined', 'object[]', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: '[object Object][]',
      },
      {
        id: 98,
        question: 'What will `console.log(+"")` return?',
        answers: ['0', 'NaN', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: '0',
      },
      {
        id: 99,
        question: 'What does `console.log(1 < 2 < 0)` output?',
        answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: 'true',
      },
      {
        id: 100,
        question: 'What is the result of `console.log(1 + true)`?',
        answers: ['2', 'NaN', 'undefined', 'false'],
        correctAnswer: '2',
      },
      {
        id: 101,
        question: 'What will `console.log(true + true)` return?',
        answers: ['2', 'true', 'NaN', 'undefined'],
        correctAnswer: '2',
      },
      {
        id: 102,
        question: 'What does `console.log(1 / "a")` return?',
        answers: ['NaN', 'undefined', 'Infinity', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: 'NaN',
      },
      {
        id: 103,
        question: 'What is the result of `console.log(!!0)`?',
        answers: ['false', 'true', 'undefined', 'NaN'],
        correctAnswer: 'false',
      },
      {
        id: 104,
        question: 'What will `console.log([] == [])` return?',
        answers: ['false', 'true', 'undefined', 'NaN'],
        correctAnswer: 'false',
      },
      {
        id: 105,
        question: 'What does `console.log("5" - 3)` return?',
        answers: ['2', 'NaN', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
        correctAnswer: '2',
      }
    ],
  };